https://druidry.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Order of Bards, Ovates & Druids
X
[woocommerce_my_account]
Join
The Druid Way
What is Druidry
What is Druidry ?
The Seven Gifts of Druidry
Druid Beliefs
Druid Ethics
What is a Bard ?
What is an Ovate ?
What is a Druid ?
Events
Members can announce their workshops, retreats, talks, or other events in the Events section of the Order’s magazines and website.
Celebrants
Celebrants can help to arrange Rites of Passage, such as Baby Namings and Blessings, Handfastings and Weddings, Funerals and Memorials.
The Library
Our archive contains manuscripts, books, and pictures, and includes many contributions from members. Some of these are offered here. They express the opinions and ideas of the authors, not the Order. To donate an article email library@druidry.org
Animals
Book Reviews
Gods & Godesses
Grail & Arthurian Studies
Modern Druidry
Sacred Sites
Trees
French Language Essays
The Order Around the World
Who runs the Order?
The Order Network
The Founder
Contact Us
Our People
The Current Chief
The Former Chief
Our Patroness
Past Presiders
The Druid Way
What is Druidry?
The Seven Gifts
What is a Bard?
What is an Ovate?
What is a Druid?
A Brief History
A Longer History
Recent History
Druid Beliefs
Ethics in Druidry
Teaching & Practice
Druidry & Other Paths
Get Involved
OBOD around the World
Who Runs The Order?
The Order Network
The Founder
The Former Chief
The Current Chief
Our Patroness
Past Presiders
Bards
Celebrants
Annual Reviews
Journals
Charities
Store
Privacy Policy
HomepagePrivacy Policy
1. By purchasing the Bardic grade course from the Oak Tree Press, who act as publishers and distributors of the course for the Order of Bards Ovates and Druids, you are also joining the Order as a member. (This only applies to the full course – not the introductory pack).
2. Your contact details (name, address and email) will be kept on the Order’s database as a member, unless you choose to resign from the Order.
3. Your contact details are held on the database so we can send you course materials and also our monthly journal, Touchstone.
4. If you request a mentor, your contact details will be supplied to your allocated mentor so they can contact you during your journey through the course.
5. All correspondence between yourself, the mentor coordinating team and mentors is entirely confidential, and will be deleted on request.
6. At the end of each grade, students are invited to send a review of their work. After being read by the mentor, these reviews are forwarded to the mentor coordinator, and are stored in a secure archive. At the end of the Druid Grade, the Druid Grade review is read by the mentor and then forwarded to the OBOD office, so they can mail you a certificate and so the Order’s Chief can read your review and write to you about it. The review is then stored in a secure archive. Reviews will be returned or deleted on request.
7. Sometimes a student asks to transfer from one language edition of the course to another, in which case their contact details will be shared with the distributor of the relevant foreign language edition.
8. If you do not join the Order, but simply order an introductory pack or item from the Order’s store, your contact details will be retained on the database, but you may request that they be deleted at any time by emailing office@druidry.org
9. Your contact details will never be given or sold to any third party.
10. Under EU data privacy laws, you have a right to change, request access to, or object to the processing of any personal data that we hold, or to ask for it to be deleted.  Should you wish to do any of the above, please contact the Secretary, OBOD, PO Box 1333, Lewes, East Sussex BN7 1DX. Email office@druidry.org.
11. Data protection outside the EU – We will take steps to ensure that your personal data is protected in accordance with the applicable data protection laws in countries that are outside the EU.
12. Our Pledge: we will protect your personal data against loss or theft, as well as from unauthorised access, disclosure, use or modification.
13. Our Data Protection Policy: we may revise or supplement our Data Protection Policy from time to time to reflect any changes in legislation or the introduction of new technology. To receive a copy of our full Data Protection Policy, or if you have any questions or concerns regarding the information given here, please contact the Secretary, OBOD, PO Box 1333, Lewes, East Sussex BN7 1DX. Email office@druidry.org.
Order of Bards, Ovates and Druids
Facebook
Twitter
Youtube
Discussion Forums
Podcasts
Cookie Policy
Privacy Policy
